tradeviewforex.com 2019-04-06

# WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
Tradeview Ltd, and its affiliate companies use your personal data to allow you
access to requested products. By clicking the consent button on this email, you
have agreed to be contacted by email. Tradeview may use your details to send
you further educational materials to help you trade. This includes:
     ● Market volatility and trading setup alerts
     ● Promotions and products to help you trade better
     ● Exclusive educational and market update webinars and newsletters
You have the option to opt-out at any time from our emails by clicking the
relevant unsub link at the bottom of the email communication.
We use your information to:
     ● Enable us to provide you with the services and information that you have
        requested
     ● Make certain that all content from out platform is presented in an effective
        manner for you and your device
     ● Analyze trends with our customers so that we can strategically improve and
        develop our website
     ● Supply you with information surrounding the products you have requested
     ●   Also provide additional information on any other products that may interest
        you, unless you have specified otherwise
     ● Maintain steady a presence of assistance, for all your service needs
     ● Alert you towards any changes of services.
WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION IS COLLECTED
Tradeview collects and processes certain items of your personal data. For some
individuals and companies that are part of our mailing list, this information is limited
to simply your name, company and email address. For individuals and companies
where we have a business relationship or we have explored the possibility of doing
business, then we collect and process more types of information. This includes
contact information: (name, address, email address and telephone number), ID

information for KYC purposes (copies of your ID card and passport and the relevant
numbers, place and date of birth, gender). This information may also include details
pertaining to convictions, court cases or claims, in order for client due diligence to
be performed.
Additional pieces of personal information may be collected and processed as part of
the course of doing business, including tax status and residency information,
professional and employment information, and financial information regarding
source of funds.
Your computer’s IP Address may be collected and logged as you interact with our
website. This data does not include any personal information about you but can be
used to identify the computer you are using.
THE SOURCES OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
The personal information we collect and process has been provided to us by you in
order that we can include you in our mailing list and update you on developments in
the sector relevant to your business or engage in business. Additional information
has been collected through our correspondence with you and as part of compliance
with regulatory requirements.
User Access Request​- Tradeview must provide the following information free of
charge:
     ● What personal information pertaining to the user is being processed
     ● Why is the information being processed
     ● Who has access to this personal information about the user
     ● Hows this personal information is being used in automated decisions
     ● What processes are using this information
 A user access request should be completed within 30 days and include a copy of
 the personal information.
STORAGE OF YOUR INFORMATION
Tradeview is the controller of your personal data. That means we take
responsibility for how your personal data is collected, used and protected. We
take great care to ensure that the security and confidentiality of your personal
data is always respected.
Once your information is placed onto our servers, we employ strict procedures
and security features to prevent all unauthorized access. We may keep your
data for longer than 5 years if we cannot delete it for legal or regulatory reasons.
If we do we will make sure that your privacy is protected and only use it for
those purposes.
You have the option to object to how we use your data, or ask us to delete it or

restrict how we use it. Please be aware under certain circumstances it may not be
possible to grant your request due to legal or regulatory claims.
As the controller of your personal data, Tradeview is responsible for its security
and we employ a number of sophisticated and robust IT practices to ensure your
data remains secure. In the unlikely event of a breach in data security and
unauthorised access takes place we will immediately implement our data security
response plan and take appropriate action to mitigate the impact. We will also
notify both you and the relevant regulatory authorities as required under data
protection legislation.
COOKIES
Cookies are small information files that a website uses to track its visitors. Our
website uses cookies and other web-based technologies to improve the overall
capabilities of Tradeview. We enable the use of third-party services (like YouTube
instructional videos) and distribute interest-based advertising on third-party
websites. When you leave our website or click on any link that will direct you
towards an external site, we are unable to control what cookies are set in. You will
need to change your cookie preferences for those sites as well.
ONLINE TRANSACTIONS
All payment transactions are encrypted. In the areas of our website that process
online transactions, make use of third party software providers. All of these
third-party services are compliant with the relevant Payment Card Industry
Standards.
AUTOMATED PROCESSING AND PROFILING
We do use automatic processing and profiling processes. These are automated
functions which analyse clients’ personal data to predict service matters relating to
the customer.
PASSWORDS
A password is required to access certain parts of our website. You are responsible
for keeping this password safe and confidential. You must not share your
password with anybody.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We do not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose your personal information to
any third party for any reason. However, we may share your details so you can
obtain access to a product or service. If you previously signed up to one of our
demo accounts (for Metatrader, cTrader, Currenex), we share your personal data

with these third-party trading platforms for the sole purpose of granting you access
to these platforms.
YOUR RIGHTS
New data protection laws confer a number of rights on subjects that have personal
data held by companies. You have the right to enquire and be told if we hold or
process any of your personal information in addition to the right to be provided with
a copy of your personal information that we hold. If any information is inaccurate
you have the right to request it be corrected and where you feel we do not have the
right to hold your personal information, or you wish us to no longer process your
personal data, you may request that the data be erased.
Tradeveiw is headquartered in George Town, Cayman Islands. You can contact us
at any time to ask any questions or raise concerns about our personal data policies
or practices, your data security and your legal rights under the various international
data protection regimes. Contact us at (compliance@tradeviewforex.com, ​ ​Grand
Cayman, KY1-1108;94 Solaris Avenue. Suite 1348 Camana Bay, Cayman Islands,
Phone :+1 345 945 6271)
Tradeview Ltd is a fully registered Broker/Dealer under the regulations of the
Cayman Island Monetary Authority (CIMA).
